
CHRISTMAS WISH is a cursive calligraphy style script that comes in two weights: a Monoline and a Calligraphic version.

For commercial use please buy a license at store.rolandhuse.com

Contains Western European accented characters and stylistic alternates for "s" and "h", standard ligatures for double letters ll tt. Please note that the font is primarily meant to type Christmas Greetings and words with, so all lowercase won't look good and swashes may overlap in some letter connections. I am working on the extension with extra swashes and ligatures and updates may follow soon.

For additional customizations extra ligatures (for logotypes for example) please email me at

contact@rolandhuse.com

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.

You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.

You MAY NOT redistribute this font.

Thank you I hope you like this font & Merry Christmas!

Roland

Instagram: @rolandhusedesign